[Music]
with data provided by the land transport
Authority it is possible to monitor the
activity of buses throughout Singapore
but considering the large volume of
information exploring individual bus
stops is a challenge for visualization
in order to achieve this an interactive
tool has been developed it acts like a
magnifying glass allowing you to explore
with great detail the activity of the
bus Network in Singapore this magnifying
glass distorts points in space to
accommodate great Zoom levels it permits
local browsing of the space maintaining
its continuity and emphasizing other
distinctive points in the periphery the
lens can be dragged over the bus network
of Singapore or focused on a spatially
restricted set of bus stops several
properties of the lens can be modified
like the radius or the magnification
level the lens can filter several types
of information like the line number of
buses currently stationary at each bus
stop the number of passengers on any one
bus and the total fairs paid by
passengers Al lighting at that stop one
can rapidly switch between these
applications and explore different
features of the transit system designed
to visualize real-time data it also
currently supports both real time and
1,000 times the realtime visualization
speed enabling users to discover the
spatial temporal patterns of Singapore's
bus Network